<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>io.github.paynssj4.Pcsx2PnachToolTk</id>
  
  <name>Pcsx2 Pnach Tool (Tk)</name>
  <summary>Convert PS2 RAW codes to PNACH format (Tkinter version)</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Convertir les codes RAW PS2 au format PNACH (version Tkinter)</summary>
  
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  
  <description>
    <p>Pcsx2 Pnach Tool (Tkinter) is a simple desktop application designed to help users convert raw cheat codes for PlayStation 2 games into the PNACH format, compatible with the PCSX2 emulator. The tool also allows adding descriptions to codes for better organization.</p>
    <p>This version uses the Tkinter library for its user interface, offering a lightweight alternative to the PySide6 version.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Pcsx2 Pnach Tool (Tkinter) est une application de bureau simple conçue pour aider les utilisateurs à convertir des codes de triche bruts (RAW) pour les jeux PlayStation 2 au format PNACH, compatible avec l'émulateur PCSX2. L'outil permet également d'ajouter des descriptions aux codes pour une meilleure organisation.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Cette version utilise la bibliothèque Tkinter pour son interface utilisateur, offrant une alternative légère à la version PySide6.</p>
  </description>
  
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.paynssj4.Pcsx2PnachToolTk.desktop</launchable>
  
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Main window of Pcsx2 Pnach Tool (Tkinter)</caption>
      <caption>xml:lang="fr"Fenêtre principale de Pcsx2 Pnach Tool (Tkinter)</caption>
       <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/paynssj4/Pcsx2PnachTool/master/Pcsx2_Pnach_Tool_Tk/pptk.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  
  <releases>
    <release version="1.0.0" date="2025-06-15">
      <description>
        <p>Initial release of the Tkinter version.</p>
        <p xml:lang="fr">Version initiale de la version Tkinter.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/paynssj4/Pcsx2PnachTool</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/paynssj4/Pcsx2PnachTool/issues</url>
  <developer_name>Paynssj4</developer_name>
  <update_contact></update_contact>
</component>
